She'll cross every line just to hear her daughter's voice again.
Stolen Girl is a thriller, action, adventure film directed by James Kent.
In 1993, Maureen’s six-year-old daughter Amina is snuck out
of the country by her ex-husband, Karim.
After years of unsuccessful attempts to find her, Maureen intersects with a professional retriever of
internationally abducted children who promises to help her find Amina in exchange for her collaboration.
Maureen, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Robeson, played by Scott Eastwood.
Carl, played by Jordan Duvigneau.
Joe, played by Matt Craven.
Dasia, played by Nowar Yusuf.
Karim, played by Arvin Kananian.
Stolen Girl is a 2025 American film  directed by James Kent and starring Kate Beckinsale, Scott
Eastwood, Jordan Duvigneau, Matt Craven, Alejandra Howard and Arvin Kananian.
The tone is intense.